<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Researches on Saraban Salsabila</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio-saraban-salsabila/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Researches on Saraban Salsabila</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/portfolio-saraban-salsabila/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio-saraban-salsabila/research/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio-saraban-salsabila/research/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;effect-of-thin-tunnel-layers-mno3-and-v2o5-on-the-enhancement-of-single-layer-organic-solar-cell-efficiency&#34;&gt;Effect of thin tunnel layers MnO3 and V2O5 on the enhancement of single-layer organic solar cell efficiency&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Layer thickness optimization has proven to be effective in the case of increasing Performance Conversion Efficiencies (PCE) of organic solar cells. In this research, optimization of the solar cell is performed and found an efficiency of 9.74%. After that, a solar cell with the insertion of some oxide layers is proposed. Two of them are the thick insulating oxide layers which have helped the efficiency to reach up to 15.23%. Under 1sun and at 1.5AM, the energy spectrum received from the sun has been calculated as 2.43eV for a 510nm light wavelength (has been considered as the peak among the visible light wavelengths), which is much more than the energy band gap of the active material. This incident is supposed to be one of the causes of the high electron tunnelling between the donor and acceptor of the LUMO (Lowest Unoccupied Molecular Orbital). Apart from its inorganic counterpart, as low charge carrier is the main concern for the organic solar cell, this can help a little by ensuring a high charge carrier and pushing the organic solar cell a step further with respect to its competitor, the inorganic solar cell.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
